Finding Aid for the Prospect Records LSC.0328
UCLA Library Special Collections
Prospect records
1959-1965
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0328
0.5 Linear Feet (1 box)
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
L.A. Wallrich, purchase, 1970.
General note
The following have added entries in the catalog:
Prospect (Cambridge, England)--Archives.
English periodicals--Archival resources.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942336233606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of correspondence and manuscripts relating to the periodical Prospect (Cambridge, England, 1959-65). Correspondents include Allen Ginsberg, LeRoi Jones, and Gerard Malanga.
English periodicals -- Archives.
- Beaudoin, Kenneth Lawrence., 3 items. (Box 1)
- Crozier, Andrew., 3 items. (Box 1)
- Davie, Donald., 3 items. (Box 1)
- Di Prima, Diane., 2 items. (Box 1)
- Dorn, Edward, 1929-., 4 items. (Box 1)
- Dowden, George., 1 item. (Box 1)
- Haag, John., 2 items. (Box 1)
- Hollo, Anselm, 1934-., 5 items. (Box 1)
- Holst, Spencer., 1 item. (Box 1)
- Jones, LeRoi, 1934-., 1 item. (Box 1)
- Malanga, Gerard., 1 item. (Box 1)
- Mead, Matthew, 1924-., 1 item. (Box 1)
- Olson, Charles, 1910-., 5 items. (Box 1)
- Prynne, Jeremy Halward., 5 items. (Box 1)
- Shayer, Michael., 6 items. (Box 1)
- Silkin, Jon., 1 item. (Box 1)
- Silkin, Jon., 1 item. (Box 1)
- Sward, Robert, 1933-., 2 items. (Box 1)
- Tomlinson, Charles., 2 items. (Box 1)